2주전, 체스터스 밀에 보이지 않는 돔이 내려 앉았다
Two weeks ago, an
invisible dome crashed down
다른 세상과 격리되었다.
on Chester's Mill, cutting us
off from the rest of the world.
왜 돔이 있는지, 어떤 미스테리가 있는지
Why the dome is here or
what mysteries lie ahead,
우린 여전히 모른다.
we still don't know.
돔은 매일 우리 안의 최선과 최악을 한계를
Every day it tests our limits,
끌어내는 테스트를 한다.
bringing out the best and the worst in us.
어떤 이 들은 우리가 영원히 갇힌 것이라고 말한다.
Some say we'll be stuck here forever,
그러나, 우리는 빠져 나가기 위한 노력을 절대로 중지하지 않을 것이다.
but we will never stop
fighting to find a way out.
체스터스 밀은 데일 바바라의 사형을 선고한다.
Chester's Mill sentences
Dale Barbara to death.
그 에그.. 뭔가를 하려고 해.
The egg... it's doing something.
이것은 돔의 새로운 지도자를 선택하게 해.
This has to be the way the
dome picks a new leader.
그녀는 당신의 군주이다.
She's your monarch.
빅 짐, 당신은 나쁜 놈이야.
Big Jim, you're a sick bastard.
나비가 어떤 스팟을 만들어.
The butterfly makes some kind of spot.
한낮에 왜 이리 점점 어두워 지지?
Why is it getting dark
in the middle of the day?
죽은 내 아내, 폴린은
My wife, Pauline, before she passed,
계속해서 한가지만을 말했어, 만트라 같은..
she kept saying one thing
over and over, like a mantra:
- "분홍별이 내려 온다."
- 우리 마을 전체는 죽은 목숨이다.
- "The pink stars are falling."
- Our whole town
만약 우리가 엉뚱한 사람 손에 들어 가는 것을 허락한다면,
is as good as dead if we let
this fall into the wrong hands.
어떻게 해야지 우리가 체스터스 밀을 보호하고 바비를 살릴 수가 있을까?
How do we protect Chester's
Mill and save Barbie?
우린 못해.
We can't.
아빠, 무슨 일이에요?
Dad, what's happening?
지금이다. 아들아. 바로 해!
Now, son, do it now!
자, 주니어!
Now, Junior!
아빠?
Dad?
무슨 일이지?
What's happening?
저 소리는 뭐지?
What's that sound?
레버를 당겨라 아들아!
Pull the lever, son.
당겨, 주니어!
Do it, Junior!
- 지금 바로!
- 두려워요.
- Do it now!
- I'm afraid.
이건 뭐지?
What the hell is that?
봐!
Look!
조심해! 움직여!
Look out! Move!
린다, 무슨 일이에요?
Linda, what's happening?
모두 의식을 잃었어
They're unconscious
숨은 쉬고 있어.
but still breathing.
짐, 도와줘요.
Jim, let me help.
머, 풀어 달라고?
What, set you free?
저기 도움이 필요한 사람들이 있잔아, 너의 사람들이
There are people out there,
your people, that need help.
좋은 시도였어, 바비.
Nice try, Barbie.
바로해 아들아.
Do it, son.
안돼, 주니어, 주니어, 저기를 봐.
No, Junior, Junior, look out there.
저 소리가 사람들을 아프게 하고 있잖아.
The sound is making people sick.
우리가 이것을 멈추어야 해.
We need to stop it.
전 못하겠어요.
I can't do it.
지금 머하는 거야?
What are you doing?
내 생각엔 돔이 우리에게 뭔가를 말하려고 하는 거야.
I think the dome's trying
to tell us something.
말도 안돼.
That's nonsense.
우리가 가야해.
We should go there.
이것이 이 일에 대한 답을 찾을 수 있어요.
It could have answers for what's happening.
돔은 답을 하지 않아.
The dome doesn't have answers.
아니요. 아빠.
Yes, it does, Dad.
이 돔은 아빠 생각보다
The dome is more
그 이상의 뭐가 있어요.
than you think it is.
돔은 저에게 뭔가를 보여줬었어요.
It's shown me things.
이거 하는 일이 그리 두려우면 내가 하겠어. 잘 봐.
If you're too scared to do
it, I'll do it. Look out.
멈춰요.
Stop.
뭐하는 거야, 린다?
What are you doing, Linda?
난 합리적이에요.
I'm being reasonable.
내가 그것을 본 이후로, 내 생각엔 주니어가 옳아요.
After what I've seen, I
think maybe Junior's right.
우리 모두 후회하는 일을 하기 전에
We'd need to take a trip to the dome
우린 돔을 돌아 보는 것이 필요해요.
before we do something
we're all going to regret.
이봐..
Come on.
이봐.
무슨 일이죠?
What happened?
몰라요. 그녀가 호수에 익사하고 있었어요.
I don't know. She was drowning in the lake.
갑자기 나타났어요.
She just appeared.
어디서 나타 났는지 몰라요.
I have no idea where she came from.
제가 시도해 보조.
Here, let me try.
당신이 여기 있어서 다행이에요.
It's a good thing you were here.
전 호수에서 이상한 빛이 나오는 것을 봤어요.
I saw strange lights
coming out of the lake.
그녀를 데리고 가서 말려야 해요. 걸을수 있어요?
We got to get her and
you dry. Can you walk?
어, 만약 멀지 않다면.
Uh, if it's not too far.
숲을 지나가면 돼요.
It's just through the woods.
뭔 일이지?!
What the hell?!
자석이에요.
It's magnetic.
우와!
Whoa!
뭔 일이야?
What's happening?
어...
Ah...
어, 린다...
Ah, Linda...
바비!
Barbie!
오!
Oh!
내 수갑!
My cuffs!
잠시만! 잡았어요!
Hold on! I got you!
도와줘!
Help me!
Help!
- 빨리!
- 안돼요.
- Hurry!
- I can't.
- 주니어!
- 도와줘! 도와줘!
- Junior!
- Help me! Help!
- Okay.
- 이리와요.
- Come on.
린다!
Linda!
린다, 거기서 나와요.
Linda, get out of here.
- 거기서 나와요!
- 바비, 안돼요. 거의 다 됐어요. 잠시만요.
- Get out of here!
- Barbie, I can't. I almost got it, hold on.
- 린다!
- 거기서 나와, 린다!
- Linda!
- Get out of the way, Linda!
거의다.. 거의 다....
Almost... almost...
거기서 나와요!
Get out of the way!
린다, 뛰어! 뛰어!
Linda, run! Run!
Go!
린다! 안돼!
Linda! No!
Sync and corrections by explosiveskull
www.addic7ed.com
처음 만드는 한글 자막.. 이상하죠? 저도 참 어색하네요...
Sync and corrections by explosiveskull
www.addic7ed.com
이름을 말 할 수 있겠어요?
Sweetheart, can you tell me your name?
어떻게 호수에 있었는지 알아요?
How did you end up in the lake?
내 말을 못 듣는것 같아
I don't think she can hear me.
쇼크 상태야.
She's in shock.
최선은 쉬는 것이야.
Best thing for her is rest.
심지어 우린 그녀가 누군지도 모르잖아.
We don't even know who she is.
맞아요. 당신 자신의 문제가 있다고 말하고 싶군요.
Right now I'd say you've
got problems of your own.
제가 좀 더 살펴 보지요.
Better let me check it out.
Okay.
이런...
Well...
바늘 실이 호수에서
looks like the stitches
느슨하게 된것이 분명해요.
must've come loose in the lake.
누가 꿰메었나요?
Who sewed you up?
이곳에 있었던 친구가..
A... friend who was here.
있었던?
Was?
네, 전 그를 떠나야 했어요.
Yeah, I had to leave him.
그는 날 보호하려고 했어요. 성공하진 못했지만.
He was protecting me; he didn't make it.
음, 요즘 같은 날에
Well, you can't be sure.
어떠한 일도 확신하면 안돼요.
Not of anything, these days.
지금 제대로 하고 있는거죠?
Are you sure you know what you're doing?
최선을 다하고 있어요.
I'd better.
전 10년 동안 EMT에 있었어요.
(emergency medical technician: 응급실)
I was an EMT for ten years.
시내에?
In town?
음. 병원의 모든 이를 안다고 생각했는데..
Hmm. Thought I knew
everyone at the hospital.
그들의 긴급 의료원처럼
Turns out the county
술취하지 않은 것으로 밝혔어요.
likes their paramedics sober.
전 여기 밖에 혼자 있는 것을 선호 합니다.
I prefer being alone out here.
어쨋거나 대부분의 시간에
Most of the time, anyway.
샘 베르드로우.
Sam Verdreaux.
줄리아 셤웨이.
Julia Shumway.
나 때문에 일어 났어.
It should've been me.
주니어, 넌 비난 받을거야.
Junior, you're to blame.
우리가 여기 오지 않았다면, 그녀는 살아 있을거야.
If we hadn't come out
here, she'd still be alive.
Hey!
주니어 실수가 아니에요.
This isn't Junior's fault.
여기서 무슨 일이 있었던 간에
Whatever's going on here,
아무도 상처 받아서는 안돼.
we gotta make sure nobody else gets hurt.
가장 최선의 방법은 우리가 시작한 일을
우리가 끝내야 해.
Well, the best way to do that
is finish what we started.
- 주니어, 도와줘!
- 다른 것을 찾아봐!
- Junior, help!
- Find someone else!
당신은 당신 손에 더 많은 피를 원하는 군요.
You want more blood on your hands
- 저 살인자를 움직이게 하는 것으로?
- Hey!
- by letting that murderer go?
내가 도디를 죽이지 않았다는 것을 너도 알잖아.
We both know that I didn't kill Dodee
라디오 방송국에 불 지르지 않은것도.
or burn down that radio station.
자 그에게 왜 내게 뒤집어 씌우려는지 말하고 싶나요?
So you want to tell him why you framed me?
사실이에요?
Is that true?
난 방금 전 교수형을 하려고 했어요
I was about to hang
- 무죄인을?
- 그건 문제가 아냐.
- an innocent man?
- That doesn't matter.
린다가 죽었어.
Linda is dead.
이 자석 풀에 마을의 얼마나
Who knows how much of this town's
더 파괴될지 누가 알지?
been destroyed by this... magnetic pull?
우린 아무도 안다치게 확실히 해야 해.
We gotta make sure nobody else gets hurt.
넌 너가 가는 곳이 어디라고 생각하는 거야?
Where the hell do you think you're going?
어디 가는데?
Where you going?
줄리아 찾으러.
To find Julia.
그가 사실을 말한것인가요?
He was telling the truth, wasn't he?
당신이 도디를 죽였어.
You killed Dodee.
그녀가 거짓 소문을 내려 했어.
She was gonna spread lies
우리 가족을 쥐어 뜯는..
about our family that would tear
- 이 마을에서.
- 당신이 체스터스 밀을 갈가리 찢어 버리는 사람이에요.
- this town apart.
- You're the one tearing Chester's Mill apart.
아니, 내가 무엇을 해야 할 수 있는 용기를 가진 사람이야!
No, I'm the one with the guts
to do what needs to be done!
누군가는 힘든 결정을 해야 해!
Someone has to make the hard choices!
니가 하겠다고?
You gonna do it?
린다가 조금 전에 했어요!
Linda just did!
다음은 누구죠, 아빠?
Who's next, Dad?
아마도 당신 이겠지..
Maybe it's you.
여깄어요..
There you go.
시내에 많은 사람들이
You know, a lot of people in town
당신과 같은 기술을 가지고 있는지 아세요?
could use someone with your skills.
음. 확실치 않네요.
Hmm. I'm not too sure
저를 보러 오는 것을 좋아 할지가
they'd be happy to see me.
과거에 무엇이 있었던,
After all this,
이 모든 후,
whatever happened in the past...
더 이상 문제가 되지 않아요.
it doesn't matter anymore.
어려운 어떤 것들은 뒤에 남기고 떠나야 해요.
Some things are kind
of hard to leave behind.
그래서 당신이
Is that why you're...
여기에 숨은 건가요?
holed up here?
혼자서?
All by yourself?
어떤 것들은 절대로 극복이 안돼요.
Some things you never get over.
내 여동생이 9년전 자살한것 처럼.
Like my sister taking
her life nine years ago.
머 도와 드릴까요?
Can I help you with something?
아, 당신 차에 대해서는 미안해요?
Look, I-I'm sorry about
your car, all right?
긴급 상활이라.
This is an emergency.
이봐요.
Hey, wait.
당신이 그 사람이군요. 글쵸?
You're him, aren't you?
당신이 그 살인자군요.
You're that murderer.
전 살인자가 아니에요.
I'm not a murderer.
게다가, 이 마을은 더 큰 문제를 맞이 할거에요.
Besides, this town's got bigger problems.
신음소리가 더 빨리 올거에요.
The groans are coming more quickly.
이것들을 재고 있었나요?
Are you timing these things?
점점 더 강해져요.. 예를 들면.. 어...
They are getting stronger, like a... a...
임신한 여성의 수축 처럼.
pregnant woman's contractions.
오직 주어진 삶 대신에,
Only instead of giving life,
사람들은 깨어자지 않는다면, 죽을수도 있어요.
people could die if they don't wake up.
그것에 대해서 대단히 자신감 있어 하네요.
You sound awful confident about that.
전 이 돔을 공부해 왔어요.
I've been studying the dome
이것이 나타나고 부터.
since it came down.
내 생각엔 전자기 필드를 조작 할 수 있다고 생각해요.
I think it can manipulate
electromagnetic fields
그리고, 그들은 어떤 사람들의 뇌파를 방해하고 있어요.
and they're interfering with
some people's brainwaves.
당신, 핵물리 학자에요?
What are you, a nuclear physicist?
매력적이죠.
Nothing so glamorous.
전 고등학교 과학 선생이에요.
I'm a high school science teacher.
레베카 파인.
Rebecca Pine.
데일 바바라.
Dale Barbara.
만약 펄스들이 여기서 이것을 할 수 있다면,
If the pulses can do this here,
돔 안에 사는 사람들에게 무엇을 할지는 말 못해요.
no telling what it's doing to
people who live by the dome.
조 맥알리스터.
Joe McAlister.
세상에, 엄마가 안에 있어요.
Oh, my God, my mom's in there.
- 엄마... 와우!
- 와우, 조심해.
- Mom... Whoa!
- Whoa, watch out.
머리를 부디쳤어.
She hit her head.
- 숙여!
- Oh!
- Get down!
일으켜보자. 알았지??
Let's get her up. Ready?
와우, 조심해!
Whoa, look out!
서둘러.
Hurry.
저 문.
That door.
머해야 하지?
What do we do?
- 테이블을 가져와.
- Okay.
- Get the table.
조심해.
Look out.
Oh.
팔을 잘봐.
Watch your arm.
조심해, 알았지...
Just get it, get it, just...
Okay.
Whoa! Whoa!
무슨 일이지?
What is happening?
모든 못을 빼내고 있어.
It's pulling all the nails out.
빼내줘!
Get it out!
내 손에서 빼내줘!
Get the nail out of my hand!
잠시만...!
Wait a sec...!
내 생각엔 돔이 내 손을 통과해 못을 당기고 있어.
I think the dome is
pulling it through my hand.
Aah! Oh, my God.
Oh, my God. Here. Here.
조!
Joe!
여기 안에!
In here!
도와줘요. 어서요, 잡고 있어.
Help him. Help him. Come on, hold that.
빼내줘, 빼내줘, 노리.. 도와줘.
Pull it down, pull it down, Norrie, help.
스토브, 스토브!
Stove, stove!
Two, three!
조심해!
Watch out!
- 언능... 어서!
- 여기로 와, 움직여!
- Come on, go!
- Get out of here, move!
어서 가자.
Let's go.
- Go.
- Let's go.
Come on, come on!
Hold-hold-hold
on.
Joe, go!
Ready, go.
Go!
Right here. Right here. Right here.
빅 짐...
Big Jim...
봐, 이제 당신과 나 뿐이야.
Looks like it's just you and me now.
난 최근 많은 스트레스에 있어... 많은 스트레스...
I've been under a lot of stress
lately... a lot of stress;
그것 뿐이야...
이것은.. 이것은 마치..
that-that-that's all
this is, it's just...
이건 스트레스가 가져온 환상이야.
it's a hallucination brought on by stress,
마치...
just...
밖에서 일어나는 일은 너 실수 때문이야.
What's happening out there is your fault.
단지, 시내 주민들이 갚는 거야.
Only, it's the townspeople who are paying.
왜 환각이 보이지?
Why wouldn't I have hallucinations?
내 어깨에 마을 전체를 짊어지고 있어.
I've been carrying this
whole town on my shoulders
돔이 온 뒤로
ever since Dome Day.
돔은 윈체스터스 밀을 부서뜨리는 중이야!
The dome is ripping Chester's Mill apart!
봐봐..
See you, sweetheart.
환상특급으로 돌아가 버려.
Go back to the Twilight Zone.
내가 할 일이 있어.
I got work to do.
제기랄.
Damn it.
당신이 이것을 했잖아.
You did this.
으~.
Ugh.
당신.
You.
그리고 난 아무대도 안가.
And I'm not going anywhere.
넌 도디가 아냐.
You're not Dodee.
넌 도디가 아니라고...
You're not Dodee...
넌 뭔가 다른 것이야
you're something else.
주니어가 말하길 돔이 그에게 말했었데.
Junior said the dome talked to him.
그에게 뭔가를 보여줬데.
Showed him things.
그는 당신에게 이것을 경고했어.
He warned you about this.
귀기울였어야 해.
Should have listened.
엄마를 의사에게 데려 가야해.
We have to get my mom to a doctor.
왜 깨어나지 않는거지?
Why isn't she waking up?
마을의 절반이 이와 같아.
Half the town is like this.
그건 펄스야.
It's the pulses.
자성은 환영, 발작을 유발 시킬 수 있어.
Magnetism like this can cause
hallucinations, seizures,
의식불명... 심지어 죽음도
unconsciousness... even death.
그래서.. 내 엄마가 죽을 거라고?
So you're saying, my mom's gonna die?
그녀의 바이탈은 안정적이야.
Her vitals are stable.
곧 펄스가 약해질거야,
그럼 그녀는 아마도 좋아 질거야.
As soon as the pulses
subside, she should be fine.
아마도?
Should be?
노리, 우린 이것을 이해해야 해.
Norrie, we are gonna figure this out.
여긴 안전한 것은 확실해요?
You're sure we're safe here?
현재로선.
For now.
펄스가 돔의 주변에 아주 강해서,
The pulses are strongest
near the dome's perimeter,
마을의 중심이
so the center of town
가장 약한 지역이야.
is the zone of least destruction.
좋아. 그럼. 모두를 이동 시키자.
Okay. All right. So we
got to move everyone.
여기로.....
To right here...
우리가 있는...
where we are...
학교로.
at the school.
돔은 체스터스 밀 주변의 자성 필드 이전으로 바뀌었어,
The dome's altered the magnetic fields
around Chester's Mill before,
모든 모나크 나비들이 돔에 반응할때,
when all the monarch
butterflies were attracted to it,
그러나, 절대로 이 정도 크기로.
but never to this extent.
만약 펄스가 점점 더 강해지면,
If the pulses keep getting stronger,
마을 전체를 허물어 버릴거야.
they could tear apart the entire town.
우린 돔의 자성 필드를 무력화
시킬 방법이 필요해.
We need a way to negate
the dome's magnetic field.
조, 우리가 했던 이 실험을 기억해
Joe, remember that experiment we did
우리가 못 주변에 구리 철사를 두를때?
when we wrapped the
copper wire around nails?
집에서 만든 자석.
A homemade magnet.
만약 우리가 정말로 큰 것을 맏든다면,
If we build a really huge one
어~ 충분히 큰 파워에 연결을 한다면,
a-and connect it to a
big enough power supply...
이것으로 아마도 돔의 펄스를 대응이 가능할 것이야.
It might be able to
counteract the dome's pulses.
맞아요.
Right.
그럼, 당신은 큰 전도체가 필요하군요..
Well, you're gonna need
a massive conductor...
쇠나 강철 등의.
something iron or steel.
그리고, 많은 구리선도.
And plenty of copper wire.
이봐.
Hey.
당신 정말로 이것이 통할 거라 생각하나.
You really think that this is gonna work,
어.. 거대한 자석?
a-a giant magnet?
글쎄, 더 낳은 방법이 있나요??
Well, you got something better?
돔은 4 손에 비전을 보여줬어.
The dome showed a vision to the four hands.
그건 빅 짐의 죽임이야.
It showed us Big Jim's death.
그런데, 우린 죽이지 않았고
그리곤 돔은 반응했지.
But we didn't kill him
and the dome reacted.
나쁘게.
Badly.
돔은 짐의 죽음을 원해.
The dome wants Jim dead.
그리고 내 생각엔 이건 안 멈출꺼야
And I don't think this is gonna stop
그 일이 일어 날때 까지.
until that happens.
난 당신 만큼이나 빅 짐이 싫어.
I hate Big Jim as much as you do.
그런데 다른 사람들 삶을 그려하면...
But taking another man's life...
얼마나 많은 댓가인지는 알아.
I know how much that costs.
그럼. 시작해 보자고
So let's just try this
과학 선생님의 방법으로
the science teacher's way first.
좋아, 시작.
All right, let's go.
- 우린 시간이 별로 없어.
- Okay.
- We're running out of time.
난 엄마 옆에 있을래
I'm not moving my mom.
너와 앤지는 여기 있어도 돼
우리가 갈거야.
Y-You and Angie can
stay here and we'll go.
- Okay?
- Okay.
난 이게 통하길 바래.
I-I hope that this works.
그를 조심해.
Watch out for him.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
It's all right.
넌 꿈을 꾼거야.
You were having a dream.
You're all right.
좋은 방법이었네요.
You've got a nice touch.
당신도요.
So do you.
모든 사람이 당신처럼 물속으로 뛰어
들진 않아요.
Not everyone would've jumped
into the water the way you did.
특별히 당신과 같은 상황에.
Especially in your condition.
당신은 내게 말해야 해요.
You gonna tell me how you wound up
당신 어깨에 총상을 입고 멀리 인적이 드문 곳에
out in the middle of
nowhere with a bullet wound
어떻게 처해 졌는지
in your shoulder?
간단히 답해서:
Short answer:
난 최후통첩을 받았어요
I was given an ultimatum.
난 이것을 바로 잡으려고 노력했고.
지금은 내가 했는지 확신이 없네요.
I tried to do the right thing
and now I'm not sure that I did.
전에 언급한 그 남자에 대해서요?
Is it about that guy you mentioned earlier?
우린 그것에 대해서 이야기 하지 말아야 해요
Well, I'm sorry that
당신은 단지 ...
You can just...
여기에 머물러요.
stay here.
쉬어요.
Rest.
그럴수 없네요.
I can't.
저기 밖에 큰 거대한 무언가가 일어나고 있어요
Something awful is happening out there
그리고, 그건 내 실수 일 수도 있어요.
and it might be my fault.
난 바로 고쳐 잡아야 해요
I have to try and fix it;
내가 유일한 그 사람일 수도 있어요.
I might be the only one who can.
왜 당신이?
Why you?
저 소녀를 돌봐줄 수 있나요?
Can you look after the girl?
그녀의 이야기를 알아봐요.
Maybe try to get her story.
Hey, wait.
Be safe.
Thank you, Sam.
_
Hey!
Are you all right?
뭘 찾고 있어?
What are you looking for?
어.. 총
Uh... a gun.
여기다가 두곤했었는데
We used to keep one here.
누구 때문에?
What for?
니 아빠.
Your father.
그리고, 만약 날 저지한다면
And you if you try to stop me.
난 널 저지하지 않을거야, 엔지.
I won't try to stop you, Angie.
아버진 거짓말쟁이야....
He's a liar...
그리고, 살인자; 그는 도디를 죽였어.
and a murderer; he killed Dodee.
You were right;
돔이 우리에게 이야기 했을 때
우린 그를 멈추게 해야 해
we should've stopped him
when the dome told us to.
우린 이걸 끝낼수 있어, 주니어.
We can end this, Junior.
내가 경찰서에서 총을 가져 올 수 있어.
I can get you a gun from the station.
그건 할 수 있어.
I can do that much.
Okay.
넌 뭐야?
What are you?
메신저.
A messenger.
듣고 있다.
I'm listening.
아니....
No, you're not.
넌 여기서 빠져 나갈려고만
계속 생각하고 있어
You're still thinking
you're gonna get out of here
그리고, 당신 앞을 가로 막는 이를
and keep on keeping on killing
계속 죽이고, 살해 할꺼야.
whoever gets in your way.
엿먹어.
Screw you.
니가 돔이든 뭐든 상관 안해...
I don't care if you are the dome...
또는 뭐든지 지옥이나 가버려.
or whatever the hell else you are.
난 이 마을을 운영할 수 있는 유일한 사람이야
I'm the only one who can run this town.
마을의 전체가 망가지고 있어
그건 너 잘못이야.
The whole town's going
down, and it's your fault.
당신은 절대로 희생하지 않아,
You've never sacrificed,
당신 삶에서는, 그런데 지금..
not once in your life, and now...
그래야 해.
you're gonna have to.
조용히 하고 꺼져!
Shut up and be dead!
난 바빠.
I'm busy.
봤지?
See?
넌 안듣고 있어.
You're not listening.
그런데 당신은 그럴거야.
But you will.
좋아. 됐어.
All right, that's it.
충분해.
That's high enough.
단지 없어져, 혼자둬.
Just leave that alone.
여기, 이 테잎을 봅시다.
Here, let me see that tape.
이것처럼 우린 전체를 감아야 해
Looks like we're all wired up.
자석의 힘이 돔에 대항이 가능한 충분한
전류를 만들수 있을거라 생각해요?
Do you think the magnet's strong enough
to generate a current
to counteract the dome?
모든 구리선은 돔에게 투자할 가치가 있어.
All that copper wire's
gonna give the dome a run for its money.
No, no, no, no,
물러나요 전부다..
No, no, no, no, let's
go. Everybody get back.
- 뒤로 물어 나요.
- 뒤로.
- Stand back, get back.
- Get back.
자석이 작동하지 않아.
The magnet isn't working.
충전은 시간이 필요해.
The charge needs time to build up.
만약 이것이 이번에 작동하지 않는다면,
If it doesn't work this time,
다음 충전 때 까진 얼마나 걸리지?
how long till the next contraction?
작동 할꺼야
It'll work.
믿어봐
Trust me.
마지막 경고입니다.
Last warning.
만약 니가 체스터스 밀의 왕 자리에
스스로 오르기 위해서 돔을 사용한다면,
당신은 누군가의 댓가가 필요해.
It won't just be you who pays
if you keep using the dome
to make yourself king of Chester's Mill.
누굴 말하는거야?
Who you talking about?
지미,
Sins of the father, Jimmy,
하나님은 항상 아들에게 방문했었어.
are always visited on the son.
Gah!
조!
Joe!
No!
_
♪ Tender we fall ♪
♪ Quiet and alone... ♪
아주머니...
Ma'am...
아주머니!
Ma'am, please!
♪ Tired and gone... ♪
엄마?
Mom?
제임스?
James?
♪ Speechless... ♪
세상에.
Oh, my God.
너구나.
It is you.
왜 저를 떠나 셨나요?
Why-why-why did
you leave me?
아니.
No.
아니다 아가야,
난 떠난적이 없단다.
No, baby, it was never you I left.
절대로, 넌 내 아들이야.
Not ever, you're my sweet boy.
더 이상은 아니에요.
Not anymore.
♪ Coming up for it... ♪
넌 날 속일수 없어, 제임스.
You can't fool me, James.
절대로...
You never could.
넌 나의 아들이야.
You're my sweet, sweet boy.
주니어!
Junior!
내 말 들리지?
Oh, God. Can you hear me?
주니어?
Junior?
정신차려.
Hang on.
Junior!
정신차려봐!
Hang on!
바비?
Barbie?
바비?!
Barbie?!
난 죽은 줄 알았어.
I thought you were dead.
이런
Come on.
그리 쉽게 죽을 거라 생각하지 마.
You're not gonna get rid of me that easy.
믿기지가 않네요
I didn't believe.
뭘?
You didn't believe what?
내가 옳다고 했던일을.
That I was doing the right thing.
돔이 당신을 보호하고 있네요.
That the dome would protect you.
자기야, 돔이 나를 살렸다고 생각하지는 않아.
Babe, I don't think it
was the dome that saved me.
그럼, 이 모든것을 어찌 설명하지?
Then how do you explain all this?
어떤 사람들은 자성으로 부터라고 말하지.
Some people say it's from the magnetism,
돔이 화가 난것이 아니라.
not 'cause the dome's angry.
조...
Joe...
겨우 숨 쉬고 있어요.
He's barely breathing.
다음 파동에는 아마도 우리도 당할꺼야.
The next wave, maybe
that takes us out, too.
그리곤...
And then...
난.. 어떻게 고쳐야 할지 모르겠어.
I-I don't know how to fix this.
아들아, 내 말 들려?
Son, can you hear me?
정신차려
Hang on.
정신좀차려
Just hang on.
Oh, God...
당신이 원하는 것이 뭔지 말해봐!
Tell me what you want me to do!
말해봐!
Tell me!
오, 난 누구랑 말하는 거지?
Oh, who the hell am I talking to?
나에게 말 할 수 있어, 짐.
You can talk to me, Jim.
넌 뭐니?
What the hell are you supposed to be?
크리스마스 미래의 유령?
Ghost of Christmas Future?
미래는 당신에게 달렸어.
The future depends on you.
내가 어떻게 하면 그를 도울수 있을지 말해봐.
Tell me how I can help him.
내게로 와, 짐.
Come to me, Jim.
네게로 와.
Come to me.
제발, 린다.
Please, Linda.
제발, 내게 말해줘...
Please, tell me...
내가 뭘 할 수 있을지 말해줘.
tell me what I can do.
오라니까.
Come.
빅 짐 레니 뭘할지 말해?
Tell Big Jim Rennie what to do?
난 그러지 않을거야.
I wouldn't dare.
빅 짐 레니 해야해 제발.
Big Jim Rennie does as he pleases.
모든것은 당신이 해야해,
Everything you do,
너 자신을 위해서라도 넌 해야해.
you do it for your own good.
당신을 봐바.
Look at yourself.
당신 아들을 봐바.
Look at your son.
이 세상에서 혼자 남은 당신은 신경쓴다고 주장하지.
The only person left in this world
you claim to care about.
시간은 흐르고 있어, 짐.
Time's running out, Jim.
결코 늦지 않았어.
But it's not too late.
뭐가 안 늦었다는 거지?
Not too late for what?
희생의 선행을 배우는 것.
To learn the virtue of sacrifice.
당신의 아들을 살리는 것.
To save your son.
짐!
Jim!
여기서 뭐하는 거야??
What the hell are you doing?
돔이 나에게 뭘 하기를 원하는 거지.
What the dome wants me to do.
난 레버를 당기질 못 하겠어.
I can't pull the damn lever.
둘 중 누가 영광을 원하지?
Either of you want the honors?
내가 하지.
I'll do it.
안돼...
No...
줄리아, 이봐.
Julia. Hey.
넌 하지 않아도 돼.
Hey, you don't have to do this.
지금?
Why now?
뭐가 문제인데?
단지 레버만 당겨.
Why does it matter?
Just pull the damn lever.
해.
Do it.
지금 바로 해.
Do it now.
해!
Do it!
안돼!
No!
난 못해.
I can't do what you do.
겁장이.
Coward.
뭐...?
What...?
돔은 우리가 널 죽이길 바라지 않아.
The dome didn't want us to kill you.
그것은 살인의 끝을 원하는 거지.
It wants us to end the killing.
미안.
Sorry.
몇시간 전을 믿기 힘들거야,
It's hard to believe a couple hours ago,
그들 모두 의식을 잃었지.
they were all out cold.
그리고 그 전 몇시간 전엔
그들은 당신의 피를 원했고.
And a few hours before that,
they were out for your blood.
내 생각보단 쉬워.
It's easier than I thought to get there.
빅 짐을 살게 하는 것이 올바른 일이었어.
You know, letting Big Jim
live was the right thing to do.
오늘을 위해.
For today.
내게 운인가봐, 그도 너랑 같이 느꼈으니.
Lucky for me, he felt the same about you.
우리 모두에게 운이 지.
Lucky for both of us.
당신은 그랜드 테프트 오토로 부터 금성장으로 갔어지, 바바바씨.
You went from grand theft auto
to a gold star, Mr. Barbara.
아, 선생님이 말하는 것을 단지 했었어.
Ah, I was just doing
what the teacher told me.
음... 돔의 자성 필드를 격퇴시킬 방법을
Um... Rebecca here is the one who came up
찾은 유일한 사람이야.
with the way to repel the
dome's magnetic pulses.
그리고 그가 가장 큰일을 하였고.
And he did most of the heavy lifting.
난 그 장비들이 준비되기를 시도했었고,
I-I tried to get a read on the rig,
그러나, 나의 자기계는 타격 받았지.
but my magnetometer's blown.
정말로 타워를 보면서 의식을 가지기를 바랬지.
Really wish I'd been conscious
to see the tower work.
어, 당신 생각에
Uh, you think
왜 멈춘것 같아요?
that's what stopped the surges?
그리고 돔두 깨끗해졌고?
And cleared the dome?
나머지 무슨 일이 있었느지?
What else could it have been?
우리보다 더 큰 뭔가가.
Something bigger than us.
다시 채워l, 엔지?
Refill, Ange?
고마워, 혼.
Thanks, hon.
Mm-hmm.
바비는 스윙 받을 만해,
Barbie deserved to swing,
그리고 당신은 그를 놔주고.
and you let him go.
뭐야, 짐?
What the hell, Jim?
필, 우린 희생양을 찾아 따라 잡아야 해.
Phil, we got caught up
looking for scapegoats.
그런데 우리가 틀렸잖아.
But we were wrong.
그리고 돔이 우리에게 말했잖아 역시..
And the dome told us so.
바비의 무죄를.
Barbie's innocent.
난 이 마을의 선량한 사람들이 알수 있게 만들거야.
I'm gonna make sure the good
people of this town know it.
단지 대단하게 우린 살아 있는 이 일들을 알아내야해.
Just be grateful we got
out of this thing alive.
우리 모두에게가 아니고.
Not all of us.
우린 우리가 놓친 것의 좋은 일을 가져오게 할꺼야.
We'll have to carry on
the good work of those we lost.
뭐라고, 필?
What do you say, Phil?
내가 너를 믿어도 돼?
Can I count on you?
오늘 타워에 볼났을 때 도움을 준 녀석들이군.
Heard you kids helped out
over at the fire tower today.
난 어.. 협력해 준것에 대해서 고마워.
I wanted to, uh, I wanted
to thank you for pitching in.
미스 파인의 생각이에요.
It was Ms. Pine's idea.
뭐든지.. 성공해어.
Whatever works.
넌 집을 잃었다고 들었는데.
I also heard you lost your house.
난 니가 우리 집에서 지냈으면 하는데.
I wanted to let you know that
my home is your home.
작고 아늑할꺼냐, 그런데, 음...
It might get a little cozy, but, uh...
잠시만, 뭐?
Wait, what?
와서 당신과 살라구?
Come live with you?
글쎄, 적어도 그건.. 어,
Well, at least it's a, uh,
거처할 곳이 있는 거네.
it's a roof over your heads.
아 ,정말로 관대해서 고마워요, 짐.
Well, that's really generous of you, Jim.
고마워요.
Thank you.
너희 집처럼 지내.
Just make yourselves at home.
슈퍼에서 봐요.
See you at supper.
자석이 당신을 이상하게 했나요?
That magnet mess with your brain?
친구들과 가까이, 하지만 적은 더 가까이 두라(속담).
You keep your friends close
and your enemies closer.
날 믿어, 엘리노.
Trust me, Eleanor.
난 괜찮아요.
My brain's fine.
미스 레니?
Uh, uh, Mr. Rennie?
안녕하세요. 음, 시간 있으세요?
Hi. Um, do you have a second?
당신 좋을대로, 미즈 파인.
As many as you like, Ms. Pine.
내 아내는 항상 말했지요
당신은 그녀의 최고의 학생이라고.
My, uh, wife always said
you were her best student.
어, 오늘 왜 그런지 배웠어요.
Uh, today I learned why.
불난 타워 자석은 우리에게 하루를 지나 갈수 있게 해줬어.
The fire tower magnet
got us through the day.
그런데, 난 오늘 안 잘꺼야.
But I'm not gonna sleep tonight.
너도 그래야해.
Neither should you.
아니, 내 생각엔 우리 둘다 오늘 저녁 잠이 필요해.
Yeah, I think both of us
need some sleep tonight.
이 서지들은 우리의 파워 소스의 대부분을 태워 버렸어.
Those surges fried most
of our power sources.
또다른 손실이 더 있을지 누가 알아?
Who knows what other damage they've caused?
난 물 공급원을 살펴봐야 겠어,
I've got to survey our water supply,
파워의 다른 소스를 어떻게 찾을지 결정하기 위해...
determine how to find
another source of power...
봐, 해돋이, 새로운 눈.
Look, uh, sunrise, new eyes.
넌 우리가 어떻게 해쳐 나갈거라고 했지?
What do you say we figure this out
over breakfast tomorrow morning?
좋아.
All right.
- Yeah.
- Great.
Coffee?
- Thanks.
- Mm-hmm.
내 생각엔 내가 음,
I think I'll, uh,
- 내가 내려가 볼께.
- 알잖아,
- I'll just go sit down.
- You know,
내가 이 교수대 위에 너와 함께 올라가 않았다는 것은
좋은 것이야.
it was a good thing that I
wasn't up on those gallows
with you.
왜냐하면 내가 낙하문을 차버리고 춤을 추었을 테니
'Cause I'd have kicked out
that trap door and danced
당신이 그 로프 끝에 메달려 있을 동안
while you hung at the end of the rope.
들어봐, 엔지.
Listen, Angie.
- 이 모든 일이...
- 아니, 나에게 떨어져!
- This all happened for a...
- No, get off of me!
미안.
I'm sorry.
지옥에나 가버려.
Go to hell.
머였지?
What was that?
오늘 내 뒤를 봐주는거지.
You had my back today.
여전히 가지고 있지?
Do you still have it?
물론.
Of course I do.
누구지?
Who's that?
내 삼촌.
My uncle.
애기.
Kid.
다 컸네.
You got big.
앉으 실래요?
You want to sit down?
아니요.
No, thanks.
누굴가를 찾고 있어요.
I'm looking for someone.
17살 이고요.
She's about 17.
긴 검정 머리, 큰 키?
Long dark hair, tall?
네, 일찍이 거리의 아래에서 봤던 그 소녀 같네요.
Yeah, that sounds like a girl
I saw down the street earlier.
그런데 그년을 알아보지 못했네요.
But I didn't recognize her.
- 어느 길로 갔죠?
- 예전 푸트 마트로 갔어요.
- Which way did she go?
- Toward the old Food Mart.
도움이 필요하세요?
Y-You want some help?
됐네.
I got it.
조망간 보마, 주니어.
I'll see you, Junior.
바비, 정차해요.
Barbie, pull over.
바로 돌아 올께요.
I'll be right back.
샘?
Sam?
Hey.
소녀는 어때요?
How's the girl?
가버렸어.
She's gone.
내 오두막 근처의 숲을 찾았었는데
I searched the woods around my cabin.
마을 전체로 찾고 있는 중이에요.
I've been looking all over town.
그녀는 몸이 좋지 않는 상태였어.
She was in bad shape.
알아요, 미안해요.
I know, I'm sorry.
그녀는 멀리 가지 못 했을거야, 우리 같이 찾아봐요.
Well, she couldn't have
gone far, we'll find her.
상기되어 보이는데, 괜찮아요?
You look flushed. You okay?
예, 좋아요.
Yeah, I'm fine.
모든게 괜찮지?
Everything all right over here?
바비, 샘 베르드랙스에요.
Barbie, this is Sam Verdreaux.
샘, 데일 바바라에요.
Sam, Dale Barbara.
이 바느질은 좋았어요.
Nice work on those stitches.
만나서 반가워요.
Glad to see that you made it.
당신도 몸조리 잘해요.
You take good care.
마지막 본것은 샘이 엄마의 장례식이었어요.
Last time I saw Sam was Mom's funeral.
금방 나타서는 지금처럼 .
Showing up just the way he did now.
글세, 넌 다신 그와 말을 할 수 없을거야.
Well, you never can tell with him.
샘은 꽤 오랫동안 두문불출했어.
Sam's been out of his
head for quite a while now.
우연의 일치 같지는 않네요.
I don't think it's a coincidence.
내가 의식을 잃었을때...
When I passed out earlier...
아-아들?
S-Son?
오늘 뭔일이 있었지.
What happened today.
미안해 니가 무엇을 말하든지.
I'm sorry I dismissed what you had to say.
아마도 니가 옳아.
Maybe you're right.
돔에 대해서?
About the dome?
Yes.
그리곤 내말 들어봐요.
Then listen to me.
내가 의식을 잃었을때,
난 어딘가 갔었어요..
When I passed out earlier,
it was like I went somewhere.
그리고, 엄마를 봤어요.
And I saw Mom.
그녀와 이야기를 했어요.
She talked to me.
그리고 나서 삼촌 샘이 저 문 앞으로
나타 났어요?
And then my Uncle Sam comes
walking through the front door?
우린 모두 오늘 어떤걸 봤어.
We all saw things today.
단지 넌 너의 엄마에 대한 꿈을 꾸었기에
Just because you dreamed about your mom
- 그게아니라, 살아 있는듯 했어요.
- 아니, 아니, 이건 꿈이아냐.
- doesn't mean she's alive.
- No, no. This wasn't a dream.
실제라고.
This was real.
- 주니어...
- 그렇게 부르지 마세요!
- Junior...
- Don't call me that!
제 이름은 제임스에요.
My name is James.
제임스.
James.
미스테리 돔에 대한 브래이킹 뉴스
Breaking news on the mysterious dome
그것은 체스터스 밀의 마을을 감싸 돌았다.
that descended over the
town of Chester's Mill.
아직까지 공식적인 발표가 없고
There has still been no official statement
비 정상적인 자성에 대한 리포트에 대해서도,
on reported abnormal magnetic activity,
또는 일시적으로 불투명한 돔이 갑자기
선명해 졌는지에도.
or why the temporarily
opaque dome suddenly cleared.
전세계는 돔에 매료되어졌다
The world remains fascinated by the dome
그리고, 여전히 안에서 갇혀버렸다고 관심을 가졌다..
and concerned for those
still trapped inside.
여보세요?
Hello?
괜찮아요?
Are you okay?
No, no, no. No! 해치지 않아요!
No, no, no. No! I'm not gonna hurt you!
Sync and corrections by explosiveskull
www.addic7ed.com
헥헥.. 힘드네요.. ㅡ.ㅡ;;;;